I felt your conquerors, Haki.
It resonated through your every punch.
A shame.
The technique was right.
But the execution was sorely lacking.
What did you call it?
Go ahead.
Keep coming at me.
I'm enjoying this.
Gum-Gum what?
Another pirate who couldn't be
Joy Boy, just like the rest of us.
Within brings out a map of your own.
To the left and the right.
All we saw, stormy nights.
All the rough winds and waves.
Coming day after day.
And the values we had
Were about to collapse?
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down.
To the compass in hand.
Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody here
knows it for certain so close
your eyes and breathe in
deeply and listen to your soul
you'll see a path in front of you and
you'll know just where you need to go
so stand up tall reach
out your hand cut through
the wind and make a stand
don't let the darkness
i'll do it my own way that's
what's best for me and you do
it your way that's how it's
got to be we're moving forward
now i'm ready but at times it's
okay to get help on the way
for the future ahead burning
bright for what's ahead you see
is beyond your wildest dreams so
stand up tall reach out your hand cut
through the wind and make a stand don't
let the darkness win just break through
we'll do it our way the best that we
know with tears and doubts and tone
we'll go where we all wanna go the
page within brings colors of our own
Hey, Raccoon, get wrecked!
He grabbed him!
He's strong.
He's overpowering Twain! That's insane!
Indeed, quite so.
You're breathing awfully hard, Raccoon.
Are you sure you're winning
this, or was that all for show?
Come on, pick it up!
Your power is lickety-spent.
Time to die.
No hiding.
Not for me.
Or for you!
You've sure been hard to
track down, young master.
Come quietly, we don't want to fight. Huh?
Wait a sec.
Is that Bobonosuke?
Yeah, he's got that smug look in his eyes.
Hold on.
The young master's handcuffs are gone.
That's right.
I'm Kozuki Udon, after all.
And that means...
that I'm free!
Shinobu. Yes?
This settles it.
I cannot meet my end yet. Meet your end?
Why would you say that?
We're here to protect you.
I sent someone, but who is it?
What's the matter, my lord?
Guess who we found, Commander?
It's Momonosuke!
I'll be there soon.
Okie Dock!
We relay a message to all
of Onigashima, Bauhuang.
Tell them my battle
against Straw Hat is over.
There's no point in struggling any longer.
They've lost.
He's firing again!
Take cover or you're dead!
There's nowhere left to go!
We're all screwed!
Chopper Amon, stop!
I've got less than ten minutes.
then my Rumble Ball's power will wear off.
It's longer than before,
but it's still not enough.
Is that really the best you can do? Huh?
Three minutes is no time at all.
Seems a little half-assed, in my opinion.
But if I'm a monster for more than ten
minutes, there might be side effects.
But who gives a damn?
What, do you only care about yourself?
Some pirate you are.
What'd you say?
Fetch me the chemicals I ask for.
The gigantification will
be extended to 30 minutes.
That's ten times longer.
It's risky, of course.
But you're not scared, are you?
Of course I'm not.
I am a pirate, after all.
Black coffee beam!
Trying to sneak away?
You've got nothing!
Now time to die!
Hey, Mary's!
Go, go, Diffusion Mode!
Onigashima!
May I have your attention, please?
The duel is over, everybody!
The enemy with the highest bounty, Mr.
Straw Hat Loopy himself,
has been defeated!
Chopperman, no!
That's not good.
Seems it's settled.
That's right, folks!
Commander Kaido just the life out of him!
Isn't that great? Ha!
You hear that?
One, two, a-s-f!
Then, Straw Hat Luffy sank like a rock,
deeper and deeper into the dark, dark sea.
Ha ha! Good news!
What, are you kidding me?
Let the idiot drown for all I care.
The Kozuki samurai are down.
Straw Hat is down.
Who's left?
Can anyone else step up?
Is anyone strong enough?
He stopped the samurai too?
Ah!
Take that, Lucy!
Commander Kaido is coming
downstairs to clean out his castle!
Look at that giant hole.
Thanks for nothing more than that.
But the good news is, our final
leader will accept your surrender!
All you have to do is
be nice and obedient,
put your hands in the air,
and promise not to fight.
Then, you'll be welcomed
as a member of our crew.
And we won't have to kill you! Huh?
Not a chance!
Lord Momonosuke! What is it? What's wrong?
Get him on!
I am here!
I have to...
I have to tell everyone!
Surrender, Land of Waddle!
This is a losing battle!
In fact, it's already lost.
Let me say it again for you.
Straw Hat Luffy was defeated and sank
to the bottom of the dark, dark sea.
This frog is a Mary, isn't it?
If there's one in the room with
us, then it's already too late.
They know where we are.
Listen.
Disgusting.
Hello, anyone in there?
I know that voice.
Hello, Momonosuke.
It's been quite a while.
It can't be, my lord.
And Shinobu, too.
What a fine reunion this is.
Father, you're alive.
Shinobu, he's not real.
You're here. You've returned.
Do not look at him.
My father.
Don't be cruel.
Let the poor boy go.
It's a heart-warming
reunion for our family.
How dare you?
Get back, Shinobu!
You don't like poor old Odin anymore?
Cease your lies! You car!
You've mocked us enough!
It's over!
Aw, Kiku, that's rude!
Why don't you put that nasty sword away?
I'm still your lord, right?
Shut your mouth!
Monster, you killed Arshina!
You're making a mistake!
It's really me, Kiku!
Don't speak my name!
Not with his face! Kanjuro! Whoa!
This is the thanks I get
after all I did for you.
Remember the first meal I
shared with you and Izo?
So, let's hear it.
Where are your parents?
Can't bring yourself to do it, can you?
I'm sorry master key just as
he said they couldn't do it
You didn't have any trouble
cutting me down the last time.
Thanks to you, we're both
critically injured, Kiku.
No!
Master Keen, I have failed
you for the last time.
Kiku Nojo of the Fallen Snow
shall meet her end this day.
However, if the fallen snow is melting?
That means dawn is coming.
To shine on the land of Wano!
Well spoken, Kiku.
And that dawn will be so bright!
That it will shine upon our
friends in the afterworld?
Kaku!
Kaku nojo!
If only we had an audience.
Surely your performance
would get a standing ovation.
And now it's time for
your final scene, Keen.
Worry not I'll set the stage
so that you die gloriously
His lord was killed and he was
betrayed by his dear friend Long as he
fought and now his comrades fall
before him one by one What a tragedy.
Or perhaps it's a comedy.
The entire audience is
waiting in suspense.
Decorate the stage with
your dazzling death.
I've heard enough!
Splendid work.
Hold on a sec.
We are not taking this freak in.
Just look at him.
Why are you being so cruel?
I said I was sorry over and over.
What more do you want from me, huh?
Kanjido!
Hell, I've missed you!
Correct.
That's the sound that
Raizo makes when he runs.
Just another one of his many skills.
It's Nimpol. Blindfolding technique.
Now, guess who?
It's Kanjido, of course.
There's no one else behind me.
oh, you trickster you
aaaaagh
there is no one more suited to lower the
curtain of my blade i give you my thanks
We shared this stage as
best friends, didn't we?
What a tale it's been.
Kiku?
Master King.
Well, well, so this is where
you scurried off to, little rat.
Shinobu, take Lord Momonosuke
and run away! Hurry!
All right.
Out of my way, samurai.
This is your last chance.
I refuse!
No matter the odds I face,
I cannot let you pass!
I'll crush you!
Come on, come on.
Come on!
Luffy!
No way.
It's gotta be a lie, right?
What are we supposed to do now?
If you're not here,
then it's all pointless.
Loopy!
Straw Hat's been defeated, they said!
Is there anyone left
who can take out Kaido?
Bao Huang's announcement filled
the samurai with uncertainty.
And in an instant, their conviction
began to waver and give way to despair.
Mr.
Straw Hat was defeated?
It can't be!
And Lord Momonosuke, is he safe?
I'm not worried.
Luffy won't lose a fight that easily.
That's right.
Don't underestimate our captain.
Onigashima continues its
journey through the sky.
Soaring over the land of Wano, it
draws ever closer to the capital.
Hot damn.
That little dumpling gave me
just the power boost I needed.
You didn't do too bad, you know.
Those guys you brought are tough as hell.
The best pirates from
their generation for sure.
They didn't lose cause they're weak.
They lost.
Cause Commander Kaido
is just too damn strong.
Slicing rounds.
Kappa style.
River of retribution.
Even if Straw Hat is dead?
Don't give up till Kaido is defeated!
Yeah, but.
Our forces haven't confirmed
Straw Hat's death yet.
They made that announcement
to crush everyone's
morale indeed true or not
there's no way to know.
This is really pissing me off you
think we're gonna lose that easy?
Oh don't cry now who's
getting their ass kicked
all the time mr wreck we
had a good thing going.
And now you're crying on the
floor like a big hairy baby.
The shepherd is slain, and now all
his sheep are left to the wolves.
That means it's time for a lickety feast.
How sweet it is.
Damn it!
Here he goes again!
Apocalyptic candy shower!
It's not me!
We can't get away!
You sorry excuse for a monster,
you're on the menu too!
Mmm, that meat looks nice and Drop!
Diablish, Umber!
Rotisserie strike!
Sanji?
You hung in there, Chopper.
Good job.
But...
Sufi...
Come on. Don't cry.
But...
He made miracles happen before.
He'll do it again.
You.
Damn you!
Look after him.
What?
Wait.
Sanji, what's this?
Once he's back, he'll have
the strength of ten men.
More like 2,000 men.
It's Sorrow!
Don't worry, I'll handle
the stupid-looking dinosaur.
So you're the one responsible for this?
Such his little reject!
He's fearless.
It's like the tides haven't turned at all.
His captain is dead.
What's he even fighting for anymore?
Did I miss something?
Now that's what I like about you guys.
Let's do this.
Come back!
Kaido!
You haven't beaten me!
Not while I still draw breath!
I made a solemn vow.
You will not lay a finger
on Lord Momonosuke.
No matter the cost!
Lord Momonosuke
Might I make a humble suggestion?
This may be uncomfortable for you!
But from this day forth, call me father.
You want me to pretend
that you are my father?
That is correct, my lord.
But it is for your own safety.
The enemy must not know your identity,
that you are Lord Odin's son.
As his descendant,
they will surely target you to prevent the
Kozuki clan from ever returning to power.
I pray you understand.
Very well then until this
battle is over call me son.
Thank you Lord Momonosuke.
Then call me father Lord Momonosuke.
All right Kin'emon I will
hey you're still calling
him Lord you two really
are quite the hapless pair?
Perhaps you should engage in
some training just to be safe.
Oh, lord.
Momonosuke, momonosuke,
momonosuke, my lord.
You seem to grasp the concept, but
you mess it up at the end every time.
Ha, ha, ha.
Friend, you're not even close.
Oh, oh.
It's too insolent for me to say.
Try harder! Keith!
Or father, I mean.
Perhaps I should be his father.
I'd much rather you be
insolent than flatulent.
My mouth was open!
Please my lord you must live.
What's the point of stalling for time?
There's nowhere left for him to run.
Don't give up Shinobu.
We must protect our lord!
As long as we live!
Momonosuke.
Father there you are.
You must survive.
You bastard!
Now die gracefully samurai.
It's hard to accept, isn't it?
The truth will find you in the end.
Robot. Huh? A frog?
Lord Momonosuke, why?
Robot.
I need to tell them.
It's out there.
Beneath the sea.
I hear Luffy.
Momo!
Luffy?
Tell them!
Everyone, I am Kozuki Momonosuke!
That sounds like...
It's Lord Momonosuke!
He's still alive!
I have a message from Luffy!
I will!
It sounds like he's crying.
I thought Kaido defeated Luffy Taro.
Luffy is still alive!
I can hear his voice now!
And he promised me that he'll come back!
So don't give up!
You have to keep fighting, no matter what!
I know it may be painful, it may be hard!
But I beg of you, as long as you
still stand, you must keep fighting!
If Lord Momonosuke wants
us to fight, let's fight!
As long as we're still standing, right?
Momo!
Tell them!
Please, Momo!
There's no way I'm losing!
I will defeat Kaido!